blogstal.com 2014-06-25

# Privacy Policy | BlogStal

  * Privacy Policy

  1. This privacy policy outlines the types of personal information we receive and collect at blogstal.com.The listing/story content and the user personal information will not be shared with anyone else and it would be private. 
  2. #### Links

All published listing contain direct linking to their site from blogstal.com. If you want to remove any listing from our website then you can contact us [here](https://blogstal.com/contact-us.php), on that time you should make sure that you are the master of such a listing. We are not responsible for all the posted listing of blogstal.com and the submitted user only has the all responsibility of their content. 
  3. #### Cookies or Browser Information

We will not collect all your browser or cookies from your system, we will collect your IP number only at blogstal.com. 

The third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on blogstal.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. blogstal.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. 

  4. For any further information please email at [info@blogstal.com](mailto:info@blogstal.com)
